All right, guys. Cart before the horse
productions is the channel. All right,
so if there's a chance you want to watch
this without my big head popping up and
all that, click the link in the
description, go over there and support
this channel. Check out the rest of
their content. I'm not too familiar with
them. Uh but this got recommended. It
was just in my feed about Amanda Seales.
And I tell you, my god, man.
>> [laughter]
>> This woman is one of the most tone-deaf
people that I have ever seen. But we're
not going to waste no time. Links in the
description. Y'all know who I do this
for. Let's go.
So let's talk about the school that
canceled me from
speaking at black graduation. All right.
Stating that they didn't have the budget
to pay me.
>> [laughter]
>> Even though
I said I would speak for free. All
right. The school that canceled me
[laughter] from black graduation is my
alma mater. No, no, no, no. So you peep
Ebony D.
If they don't have the budget and you
said you would do it for free, ma'am,
they would pay to not even be around
you.
She be confused.
Look, let me shut up. Let's let it keep
playing.
Let me let it keep playing. Boy, I'm
coming in with a whole sermon. Uh let's
go. Purchase.
SUNY Purchase
reached out to me, their black
graduation committee,
to speak at black graduation. Now, some
of you all may not know, but some
schools will have a special graduation
just for the black students. And um I
have spoken at several black
graduations. 2 years ago, SUNY Purchase
asked me to come speak at their black
graduation. Again, SUNY Purchase is my
alma mater and again, I am the I was the
commencement speaker at my own
graduation at SUNY Purchase.
So SUNY Purchase reached out to book me
to come speak at their black graduation.
In 2023, I spoke at black graduation.
They also gave out an award in my name,
called the Amanda SEALES ACTIVISM AWARD.
>> [music]
>> SO, SHE TRYING TO BUILD it up. They
canceled on you. All right, she said,
"Look, I was there 2 years ago. Look,
I'm great. They made it." And now they
said they ain't got enough money. He
said, "But I'll do it for free." They
said, "Yeah, but given that cost,
there's going to be some cost. They
ain't free. Who you think you're talking
to?"
That was That was then. She talking
about they gave her awards. That award
probably don't exist anymore. Probably
not. Hey, yo, let me move forward here
though. And no disrespect to their
commentary. I
strongly advise y'all to go check their
commentary out. But we going to keep it
quick cuz I got some other [ __ ] to pull
up about
Miss Seales here.
cuz I was staying in the city. Get me
from the city up to the school. The
school is required that time was kind of
a
you know, ceremony or whatever because
you're not black, Amanda Seales,
respectfully. And the only thing I
required that time was for them to get
me
from the city cuz I didn't live in New
York at the time. So, I I asked them to
get me from the city cuz I was staying
in the city. Get me from the city up to
the school. The school is an hour away
from the city.
When I got there, they had provided me
with um
like hors d'oeuvres, you know, like a
fruit plate, etc. Which is standard.
Now,
I spoke at the graduation. We handed out
the Amanda Seales Activism Award. It was
really honestly a beautiful experience.
And considering how much SUNY Purchase
put me through at its school, I felt
like there was a certain kind of
full circle moment happening. So, when
they reached out again this year, we
asked, "Oh, are you all handing out the
Amanda Seales Activism Award?" And they
said, "Oh, we don't know anything about
that." FINE.
WELL, [laughter]
WE SAID,
MY
>> REPRESENTATIVE told them, well, the only
thing we would ask is that we get to
hand out the award again. Otherwise,
Amanda will do it free of charge."
She then sent them my writer. Let's talk
about what a writer is. A writer is
Let's stop her before she get into this.
Now, what I'll get you is sister
Courtney, don't seem like they want her
there. What you think? No, absolutely.
It I was thinking the same thing Mr.
Walker was thinking. That award is long
gone. When When she said that she would
do it for free, I was like, nah. If you
said you'll do it for free, if they
didn't have the money in the budget to
accommodate you and you said that you
would do it for free, they already knew,
we're not giving out this award. So,
there's no need for you to come here
because it's nothing to see.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm sorry, but there's nothing to see
and that's exactly what And look, if you
guys aren't familiar with Amanda Seales,
like if you watch this video, you're not
familiar with Amanda Seales, you're
probably not going to understand why why
everybody's face looks the same.
From Ebony Dean to Hanging with
Courtney, to Gavin X and Mr. Walker,
everybody's looking the same including
myself. This woman does not understand
the influence that she has on people.
And what I mean by that is she doesn't
understand that she's unlikable.
That she's insufferable. It's not
because you're so brilliant. It's not
because you're so educated. And no,
ma'am, it is not because you're a black
woman. It is because of your attitude.
It is because of your entitlement. It is
because you are annoying as a
[ __ ] You're not self-aware,
okay? You You don't think you should
ever be held accountable and it is
everybody ELSE'S FAULT.
EVERYBODY ELSE'S FAULT FROM WHY she's
not getting invited to parties. Remember
that? I know some of y'all probably
remember that. She caused a big stink
because she's not being invited to
parties. Ma'am, they are strategically
making sure that Amanda doesn't come to
the party. That's how unlikable she is,
man.
Let's keep watching.
Yeah, and Amanda Seales, just face it,
boo. It's over. All, you know,
you cos playing as us and you talking
crazy about us and stuff. At the end of
the day, they don't want you in that
school. Go where you're celebrated. Go
to back to Grenada and and get some
awards and stuff popping down in your
home country or whatever because when
you had a chance to kind of do right by
the foundational Black Americans, you
didn't do it. And so now they don't want
you speaking. They don't even want to
give out the award no more. So it's
over. Pack it up and get on that Tom
Joyner back to your homeland.
That [laughter] was temp. And that's a
good point, right? Like what she's
saying. Like I don't I consider Amanda
Seales as a black woman, right? I
consider us all on the panel. Me,
myself, I'm half Filipino. I'm a black
man. Okay, that's the life that I live,
right? But the problem with people who
aren't originally from America speaking
on Black American issues, you can cos
play as a Black American
as an opportunist, right? Because it
makes sense right now, but then you can
also
pretend that you're not a Black
American. Oh, no, I'm not a Black
American. I'm from Grenada. Oh, I'm from
the Caribbean. Oh, I'm from You know,
and I get that you're not from here.
Okay, then don't discuss [ __ ] like you
are. Does that make sense?
It's it's it's it's a, you know, there's
a little bit of nuance there. I would
still consider her a black woman, but if
if if if you're a Black American, you
should be a Black American 365 days a
year. Like I understand like you also
want to be bigger than race, right? Like
race should not be the only thing that
defines you. That's not what I'm
what I'm suggesting. What I'm suggesting
is
all of this, you're a Black American day
today and then tomorrow you're not
because it makes sense for you.
I'm not with that. True. That was a
temporary award. They gave that as a
one-time deal. That wasn't nothing that
was going to become a staple.
And no, that was a one-time They only
did it probably because she was on that
one show Insecure. You don't understand.
Colleges are opportunistic. It's true.
OH, YEAH, WE GOT AMANDA SEALES. YEAH,
you on one of the hottest shows today.
RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
ALL THAT for show. But now that time has
come and gone. What have you done
lately? Been a buffoon. And that has to
be so embarrassing just to say, "Hey,
I'll do it for free." Let's give out
this award. And they're like, "No, we
know nothing about this." That's like,
you know how these cities give away
these days like, "Oh, you're getting a
day." And the day comes up and it's no
longer there. You know, like that's
embarrassing. [laughter]
So, I know she felt pretty bad about
that, you know. I hate that for her, but
hey. And she has a history of not being
able to work with people like Mr. Walker
was saying. On Insecure, her and Issa
was bumping heads and she was in the
music group Floetry, I believe. So, was
that her? Was she?
>> all about that. Me? Oh, I don't know. I
don't think so. I would love them cuz I
like them.
>> Ain't no no I'm not not Floetry. Ain't
no way. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That was my girl
Marsha Ambrosius. Ain't no way.
>> Yeah, yeah. I was going
I ain't getting nothing sultry and sexy
about no damn Amanda Seales. Absolutely
not. That's going to break my heart. I'm
going to have to cancel Marsha on her
behalf. But yeah, she was. Who was? It
was some Yeah, she was in Floetry. They
kicked her out the group. What? Yeah,
Amanda Seales has been a tyrant her
whole life. Like I said, she Every time
she get to working with somebody, she
they they throw her out. Like Issa
kicked her off the show. They had a
problem with her and Yeah, I I don't
think she's really been liked since My
Brother and Me cuz she was on My Brother
and Me with Alphy in in that Nickelodeon
show back in the day. I
>> Hey, y'all. remember that.
>> Yeah, I I just looked this [ __ ] up. They
they said
Hey hey, Floetry is one of my favorite
groups also. But anyway, Flo
Marsha Ambrosius said that she was in
the group for 3 weeks.
For 3 weeks. And [ __ ] happens, but I'm
telling you, this is her pattern. This
is her pattern. You was It Look Look at
at the opportunities that you had.
Floetry, okay? So, something happened
there with your attitude, okay?
Insecure, great show.
Something happened there, okay? Also,
this highfalutin Hollywood party,
something happened there that they
didn't want you there, okay? And now
here we are
with her alma mater.
Her alma mater said, "Ma'am, even though
you'll do it for free,
we don't have the budget."
That's crazy.
All right. So, at what point is it you?
At what point is it you? Come on. But Oh
man, yeah. Amanda, it it's a wrap, boo.
Oh, she was 2007.
There y'all go.
BRIEFLY. BRIEFLY.
BRIEFLY.
>> [laughter]
>> SHE [snorts] THEN SENT them my rider.
Let's talk about what a rider is. A
rider is basically like the hospitality
requirements for somebody when they are
going to take part in an event, etc.
Some people's riders are out of this
world. Like, Beyoncé's rider includes
like they have to put a new toilet seat
in. Like, Jennifer Lopez's rider is like
the entire room has to be white. Like,
crazy [ __ ] like that. Famously,
I think it was the Rolling Stones or Van
Halen, one of these groups, had a rider
where it was like, "Oh, M&M's, there
can't be any green M&M's, okay?" That's
a rider.
I have purposely
made my rider
under $100. And they still not [ __ ]
with you, Amanda.
And they still not fooling with you.
You said you would do it for free and
they still not fooling with you.
How does she process this?
I don't think she is processing it. She
just gets on her phone. This is what
happens when there ain't nobody to to
pull your coattails. This is what
happens when there ain't nobody to check
you. This is what happens when there
ain't nobody to correct you.
You know what I mean? This is what
happens when you don't have enough
people around you that love you to be
like, "Hey, man, you you you need to
look in the mirror.
You're having all of these different
things. You can't maintain
relationships, right? Like your business
is not
business is not booming as it was,
right? Because of your relationships and
how you treat people and you've garnered
this reputation that you just treat
people however you want to treat them
because you're overestimating your
talent.
Could that be Could that be true?
Oh, I think it could. I think it could.
Let's keep watching.
My rider is literally
Oh, god.
>> a fruit plate,
a vegetable plate,
>> [laughter]
>> some apple juice,
some water,
some tea,
and um spicy nacho or sweet Sorry, sweet
chili
um Doritos. Okay, well, hey, I may
change my mind about Amanda because
those are fire. So, she'll So, she has a
a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a
a a a a a a a a a a a a a a good
Who cares that you got a cheap rider?
Who cares that you'll do the [ __ ] for
free? They don't want you there. So, my
question is, why do you think these
people owe you?
That's literally what we're talking when
we talk about entitlement. Why are you
owed the opportunity
to speak there?
You're not about to say [ __ ]
You're not about to say nothing
thought-provoking. Okay, I don't look at
I I I [ __ ] with your button. I like your
button, but all that Oh, yeah.
Amanda Seales is brilliant before you
criticize her. Get the [ __ ] out of here.
Brilliant how and brilliant where? I
don't care she got a degree. I don't
care if she had 10 of them.
Do you Have you guys not met a complete
[ __ ] that had several degrees?
Y'all need to get out more. Just because
somebody is is degree'd up or whatever
the case does not mean they're
intelligent. That means they're good at
going to school.
That's my rider.
Okay? I have purposely made my rider
affordable.
Uh hold on. Hell! You say all that,
don't forget that rose.
Bomb Jacqueline. She said, "Make sure
there's a freshly charged The battery
better be fully charged [laughter] in my
room waiting on me. Hey, did you see
that? Hold on, that is too funny. Sir,
that is
That is out of line, sir. How dare you?
>> Doritos.
Watch this. That's my rider.
That rose.
If some of you chicks rose had a nose,
my God. That man is crying. Come on.
Yeah, drink some water. She said, "Make
sure there's a freshly charged
The battery better be fully charged in
my room waiting on me in the box still.
All right, she's talking about fruit
plates and fruit cups and smoothies.
Sir.
Sound like a diva. I got to let my rider
My rider is cheap.
Suni is not for you. Because one, people
don't be having money. Two, I don't need
all this extra [ __ ] But three, and
three, I do deserve to have some basic
creature comforts when I'm coming to
work. You deserve? They don't want you
to come Ma'am, they don't want you to
work there.
What are you talking about?
Creature comforts? Ma'am, the creature
comforts you get at home. You be that
creature that you be it at home. Be
comforted at home.
People don't have People like this, man,
they think that it's something wrong
with other people if they don't want to
be around them.
My god.
We just got an email from them earlier
today Right. saying that we cannot
afford you afford for you to come Oh,
I'm leaving out. I'm leaving out. Even
though I said I was going to speak for
free
>> Yeah. they said, "We're actually going
to offer you a thousand dollars."
>> OH. SO, EVEN THOUGH I said I will I will
speak for free, they said, "We will give
you a thousand dollars."
>> Okay. What? TO NOT COME?
TO NOT SHOW UP? MAN, we will pay you if
you just stay away. Please, don't say
that you went to school here. Please,
don't show up. Okay? You just just Here
here here's a thousand dollars. You you
can get all the spicy chili Doritos that
your heart desires, but just don't come
back here. Don't ever ever ever ever
ever ever ever ever ever ever
come back here. Come on. WE SAID,
"OKAY."
The email that we received today
is due to budgetary reasons we can no
longer have YOU SPEAK.
>> RIGHT.
TO WHICH MY REPRESENTATIVE REPLIED,
"THAT DOESN'T make any sense. What is
the real reason?" Because
>> Ma'am, because you're you. Because
you're you, you have no self-awareness,
you're unwilling to change. Okay? You
annoy everybody. All right? Like Listen,
I've said this before with other people,
but yo, I really mean this with Amanda.
If there's a party going on
and we all kind of know each other, you
know what people are doing? Hey, is
Amanda over there? Amanda ain't coming,
is she?
No, no, no, we didn't tell her. Okay,
cool. Cool. cool, cool. I'll be there.
What you want me to bring? That's what
people are doing.
Okay, if Amanda's showing up, I'm
leaving. If Amanda shows up, just let me
know how it went. Okay? Don't tell
Amanda because she's going to kill
everybody's fun. That's who Amanda is,
man. But honestly, we haven't asked you
for anything.
Uh
and now you're saying that it's your
budgetary reasons.
And the And for what it's worth, let me
also add Oh god. Sending a writer Mhm.
They We always have people come back.
>> Mhm. And they may say something like,
"We can't afford all of the writer. Um
you know, is it okay if we just make
sure to provide XYZ?" Sure. Okay.
Even though, by the way, the can't
afford is like What what What are we
talking about?
>> I'm annoyed already.
>> this The reason this live is called Know
Your Worth is because
they then came back and said, "No, it
really is because of the budget. We
cannot afford your writer your writer.
So, we just
>> They couldn't afford the $100.
You hear me? They couldn't afford the
$100, ma'am. What do you mean, know your
worth?
You need to I think that's a good idea
that you really truly need to know your
worth because what you think your worth
is could very well be inflated. Like you
over here cry blood clot crying and
begging not begging, but crying and
complaining
about these people not having you there
when you got a $100 writer. You agreed
to do the [ __ ] for free. And then you
said they was going to pay you $1,000
and then changed their mind.
So, maybe you're not worth what you
think you're worth.
Come on. excited. I want you to hear
this.
The budget is our real reason. We
unfortunately were not given enough
money to have Miss Seals attend due
>> no, the budget is the excuse. It's not
the reason.
It's not the reason. Look, hanging with
Courtney, you know what I'm talking
about. It is not the reason, ma'am.
That's the excuse. to the request made
in the writer, as well as among other
things for the event that we had to pay
for such as catering and decorations.
Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know who their advisor is.
>> Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Uh-huh, what about it?
>> But they're doing a
terrible job. I think they're doing a
great job, ma'am. I think that they talk
to themselves, you know what I mean?
They they sit around the table, they was
like, "Are we going to Are we going to
have Amanda Seals?"
WE AIN'T HAVING AMANDA SEALS. WHAT DID
SHE CALL that [ __ ] The Amanda Seals
civil rights activist or whatever the
[ __ ]
MAN, HELL NO. WE AIN'T HAVING NO Amanda
Seals here. You hear how she act? You
hear how she treat people? You hear how
she talk? You hear how she won't shut
up? Like go to her YouTube page. Look at
the [ __ ] that she's crying and
complaining about. Did you hear about
it? Did you hear how how annoying she
can be? That's what people are talking
about.
Because that's their experience with
you.
That's their experience with you. At
some point, if everybody's having the
same type of experience with you,
you have to There's There has to be
something THERE THAT'S FACTUAL. OKAY?
THIS is not the Twilight Zone. It ain't
something wrong with everybody else.
Ma'am, it is you.
>> [music]
>> Hey yo, yo, listen, y'all. Go check out
this podcast, y'all.
Cart before the horse here. Let me go
ahead and sub to them. Let me go ahead
and hit that bell on them. You know what
I mean? I like to support people on the
come up. They're doing the work. Um
And you know, I I do this the most ethic
in the most ethically
I consider myself
the most ethical YouTuber that does
reaction content because I tell people
early.
I tell you I'm not trying to trick
nobody to hear what the [ __ ] I'm talking
about or seeing what I'm You're going to
know who I am eventually. You know what
I mean? You're going to know that it's
not the original creator's video. So,
let me let you know that up front. Go
over there, support them, watch them.
You can come back here and see how I
reacted to the [ __ ] and you can see the
difference between the original creator
and what Heavy Gan had to say.
But, let's keep moving here cuz I got
some other [ __ ] dude. Like, people may
people may be like, "Hey, I don't
understand this." So, listen, dog. This
is how this woman treats people.
Okay? She's in the position that she's
in and she has the reputation that she
has because of the way that she treats
people. Now, WATCH THIS.
WILL BRACKET,
YOU curly-headed [ __ ]
All right. So, Will bracket's been
harassing me along with other people.
Well, not harassing me. I appreciate you
guys.
Uh um about merch.
And the reason that I haven't done the
merch, right, is because I'm It's only
me. I'm the only guy in the factory and
I like doing videos. Now, if I got to
come away from this and do
administrative [ __ ] I hate doing that.
Okay? Um so, I just haven't made the
time to do it is really the answer. It's
not anything else.
Um I don't want to take any time away
from doing this, which is why I haven't
done anything. And more importantly, I
don't want people breathing down my back
behind money they've already spent that
I haven't delivered on. Okay? It's my
personal All right. Now, it happens not
[ __ ] in other areas, but dog, I don't
want you paying paying me for anything
that I'm not delivering to you. So,
watch this. Now, watch her, okay?
What's the hold up? This is how much
better I am than the Seales.
>> [laughter]
>> That's basically what it sounds like.
Listen to this, dog. Listen to this.
Now, this is this is Amanda.
God bless her. This is Amanda
responding
to people in her audience that have that
were that like her enough, like what the
[ __ ] is going on with y'all? But that
like her enough
that they wanted to buy merch.
Now, they're asking "Where's the merch
at, Amanda?
We're waiting for our whatever it is
that you sold to us."
Listen to this woman's response.
"What's the hold up?
Question mark.
Please let me know where my order is."
"You don't even got to worry.
You don't even got to worry.
What? Cuz now you don't got no order to
worry about."
>> [laughter]
>> What does that even mean? So now the
person just bought some [ __ ] that you
just don't have to send to them because
you don't feel like you should answer to
that?
Listen to this, dog.
And and look, she read the comment.
What did this person say that was wrong?
They asked you where their order was and
you said, "Oh, well you ain't got no
order now."
And this is how you're treating your
people? All this black power this and
black power that and black empowerment
and da da da da and racism white
supremacy blah blah blah. How do you
treat black people, ma'am?
God damn, I can't even buy a shirt from
Amanda ass
and ask her where the shirt is. Rewind
this back. We got some time today,
y'all.
"What's the hold up?
Question mark." What is wrong with that
question? If that person's been waiting
for an extended amount of time for
whatever the product is, yeah, they get
to ask you what the hold up is. They
didn't cuss at you.
Please let me know where my order is.
Please.
You don't even GOT TO WORRY.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU DON'T EVEN GOT TO WORRY. HOLY [ __ ]
You don't even got to worry.
Cuz now you don't got no order to worry
about.
>> God damn.
>> That's it.
WHAT'S THE HOLD UP?
>> [laughter]
>> WHO THE [ __ ] ARE YOU TALKING TO?
YOU. The person that they bought the
product from.
They bought it from you.
And they want to wear it or whatever
they whatever it is that they bought.
And you're asking who they're talking
to?
What?
Ma'am, stop acting like you represent
black women when you get to talking.
Stop, you're [ __ ] up the social
image, okay? You're [ __ ] You're messing
up the social and public image of black
women when you get on your whatever it
is
and get to talking like this.
Understand, in her audience, what's
mostly in her audience are black women.
Black people.
Look at this.
If this is how you treat people that
that support you,
my god, how do you How do you treat
other people?
Think it's funny. So, when you guys are
communicating with small businesses this
this um
this holiday season, just remember
just remember
that nine times out of 10 you're talking
to the person who's actually uh doing
the job. Okay. So?
And someone said, "Sounds like a valid
question." And that's why your ass will
get refunded, too.
Because if you think, "What's the hold
up?"
>> Yo, that is crazy.
And then you want to then you want to
preach to people about how they need to
respect small businesses because you're
a small business. Shut up.
What are you talking about? If you're a
small business owner, all right, let's
let's talk about that. If you're a small
business owner I'm tired of
unprofessional people trying to act like
oh well I got a black business. I got a
black business. You need to support
black business. I'm not supporting no
unprofessional business.
I'm not supporting no business that
don't respect their customers.
Okay? So never mind all that oh well if
you're talking to a black I understand
you need to be respectful, okay, as a
patron, all right? That's not I'm not
excusing that. What I'm saying very very
clearly is that if you're a business, a
small business especially, regardless a
black business a white business I don't
care. If you're a small business
it is your customers that put food on
your table. It is your customers that
allow your rent to be paid, your
mortgage to be paid, your lights to be
paid, for you to be fed, for you to be
secure. It is your customers that do
that. How dare you talk down to those
people?
You don't deserve [ __ ] You don't
deserve nobody in our audience. That's
why her YouTube channel is essentially
dead, okay? This is why she can't get
hired nowhere. That's why don't nobody
want to invite her nowhere. All right,
think of how unhappy you must be as a
human to talk down to somebody who
supports My God.
I don't ever want to be this.
I'll be a lot of things, y'all, okay?
I'll be a lot of things. A lot of people
may not like certain [ __ ] or whatever
the [ __ ] People that support me, I [ __ ]
with you.
I [ __ ] with you. Y'all are helping me.
Y'all support this. Y'all get it. Y'all
are a part of my audience. I owe you.
Not the other way around.
Let me know what you guys think.
Remember, gratitude is a superpower,
y'all.
>> [laughter]
>> Gratitude is a superpower. Let me know
what you think. Remember, you can say
whatever you want to say. The only rules
are you got some [ __ ] TO BE NICE. ALL
PRAISE TO THE ALMIGHTY ALGORITHM. LIKE,
SHARE, SUBSCRIBE. YES, WE ON THE WAY to
a milli, baby. Let's get it.
>> [groaning]